Another, more natural option for your Easter basket grass is to get a paper product grass.
Basically, what this is is a paper product, usually a very thin paper, which then is sliced up, and you can see you have a type of grass.
Now, this is not real grass, but you're getting closer to the real thing than plastic grass, certainly.
So this is a more natural environmental option for your Easter basket.
But keep in mind, just because it looks a little more nature friendly, and some of these things you can certainly recycle; not necessarily always the best thing for the environment still.
And what do I mean by this?
I mean that oftentimes there's processing, and dyes, and all sorts of things.
They can still go into this grass, so if you're really worried, and you want to help out the environment, the easiest way to do it is make your own grass.
Have like a basic piece of paper, a white piece of paper; no problem at all.
You can also get like a dyed construction paper, if you want to.
Any which way, you have this, you slice it up with a scissors, and then that's very easy to do.
You have your natural Easter grass.